(air whooshing)
(plane engine roaring)
(upbeat music)
♪ A lonely mother gazing
out of her window ♪
♪ Staring at a son that
she just can't touch ♪
♪ If at any time he's in a
jam she'll be by his side ♪
♪ But he doesn't realize
he hurts her so much ♪
♪ But all the praying just
ain't helping at all ♪
♪ 'Cause he can't seem to
keep his self out of trouble ♪
♪ So, he goes out and he makes his money ♪
♪ The best way he know how ♪
♪ Another body laying cold in the gutter ♪
♪ Listen to me ♪
(gun bangs)
♪ Don't go chasing waterfalls ♪
♪ Please stick to the
rivers and the lakes ♪
♪ That you're used to ♪
♪ I know that you're
gonna have it your way ♪
♪ Or nothing at all ♪
♪ But I think you're moving too fast ♪
♪ Little precious has a natural
obsession for temptation ♪
♪ But he just can't see ♪
♪ She gives him loving that
his body can't handle ♪
♪ But all he can say is,
"Baby is good to me" ♪
♪ One day he goes and takes
a glimpse in the mirror ♪
♪ But he doesn't recognize his own face ♪
♪ His health is fading
and he doesn't know why ♪
♪ Three letters took him to
his final resting place ♪
♪ Y'all don't hear me ♪
♪ Don't go chasing waterfalls ♪
♪ Please stick to the
rivers and the lakes ♪
♪ That you're used to ♪
♪ I know that you're
gonna have it your way ♪
♪ Or nothing at all ♪
♪ But I think you're moving too fast ♪
♪ Come on ♪
♪ I seen a rainbow yesterday ♪
♪ But too many storms have come and gone ♪
♪ Leavin' a trace of
not on God-given ray ♪
♪ Is it because my life
is 10 shades of gray ♪
♪ I pray all 10 fade away ♪
♪ Seldom praise Him for the sunny days ♪
♪ And like his promise is true ♪
♪ Only my faith can undo ♪
♪ The many chances I blew ♪
♪ To bring my life to anew ♪
♪ Clear blue and unconditional skies ♪
♪ Have dried the tears from my eyes ♪
♪ No more lonely cries ♪
♪ My only bleedin' hope ♪
♪ Is for the folk who can't cope ♪
♪ Wit such an endurin' pain ♪
♪ That it keeps 'em in the pourin' rain ♪
♪ Who's to blame ♪
♪ For tootin' 'caine in your own vein ♪
♪ What a shame ♪
♪ You shoot and aim for
someone else's brain ♪
♪ You claim the insane ♪
♪ And name this day in time ♪
♪ For fallin' prey to crime ♪
♪ I say the system got you
victim to your own mind ♪
♪ Dreams are hopeless aspirations ♪
♪ In hopes of comin' true ♪
♪ Believe in yourself ♪
♪ The rest is up to me and you ♪
♪ Don't go chasing waterfalls ♪
♪ Please stick to the
rivers and the lakes ♪
♪ That you're used to ♪
♪ I know that you're
gonna have it your way ♪
♪ Or nothing at all ♪
♪ But I think you're moving too fast ♪
♪ Oh you're moving too fast ♪
♪ Don't go chasing waterfalls ♪
♪ Please stick to the
rivers and the lakes ♪
♪ That you're used to ♪
♪ I know that you're
gonna have it your way ♪
♪ Or nothing at all ♪
♪ But I think you're moving too fast ♪